<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ramtin Ehsani</title>
    <link>https://ramtin-ehsani.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ramtin Ehsani</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ramtin-ehsani.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Build and Host a Website with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://ramtin-ehsani.github.io/posts/hugo-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ramtin-ehsani.github.io/posts/hugo-website/</guid>
      <description>This is a concise, step-by-step guide on how to build a website - just like this one - with Hugo, and host it on Github. Follow the steps and check out the links for further explanation on each component. This guide is made for non-experts, because I found most Hugo tutorials utterly useless and sparse for people new to computers web-development.&#xA;It might look daunting at first to go through all these steps below, but the reward is that once you get it right, updating and maintaining your website will be incredibly fast and easy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ramtin-ehsani.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ramtin-ehsani.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I’m a PhD candidate in Computer Science at Drexel University and a research assistant in the SOAR Lab. My research focuses on automated program repair, where I study how large language models can generate reliable, trustworthy program fixes. Beyond program repair, I am broadly interested in advancing AI-driven approaches that enhance issue resolution, developer productivity, and the reliability of software engineering tools.&#xA;Download CV Link to heading Education Link to heading 2023-present PhD in Computer Science, Drexel University | Philadelphia, USA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://ramtin-ehsani.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ramtin-ehsani.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email: ramtin.ehsani at drexel.edu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://ramtin-ehsani.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ramtin-ehsani.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Ramtin Ehsani, Esteban Parra, Sonia Haiduc, and Preetha Chatterjee (2025). Hierarchical Knowledge Injection for Improving LLM-based Program Repair. In Proceedings of the 40th IEEE/ACM International Conference on Automated Software Engineering. ASE 2025.&#xA;Ramtin Ehsani, Sakshi Pathak, Esteban Parra, Sonia Haiduc, and Preetha Chatterjee (2025). What Makes ChatGPT Effective for Software Issue Resolution? An Empirical Study of Developer-ChatGPT Conversations in GitHub. Under minor revision in Emprical Software Engineering Journal. EMSE 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research Projects</title>
      <link>https://ramtin-ehsani.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ramtin-ehsani.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>SOAR Lab&#xA;I work in the SOAR Lab, where we advance software engineering with large language models and data-driven methods. Below are some of my recent projects and publications:&#xA;Hierarchical Knowledge Injection for LLM-based Program Repair ASE 2025&#xA;What it is. A layered retrieval pipeline (bug → repository → project) that supplies LLMs with the right level of context for the purpose of automated program repair.&#xA;Why it matters. Improves correctness across different bug types and shows which levels of context LLMs actually need to generate effective repairs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
